Contact

09824354087 (Mobile) nelson.seo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ nelsonchristian (LinkedIn) about.me/nelsonchristian (Personal) www.facebook.com/nelson.seo1 (Personal)

Top Skills

Digital marketing
Online Marketing
Online Advertising

Languages

Hindi (Full Professional) English

Nelson Christian L.I.O.N. ✓

Digital Marketing Team Lead at Azine (16K+ Connections), Always Learning, Available for new Task...!!

Ahmedabad

Summary

Be A Good Learner, Digital Marketing Expert, Online Marketing, PPC, Internet marketing & Branding, Web Analyst, Search Experience Optimization, Internet marketing consultant

Specialties: Internet marketing & Branding, Social Media Marketing, Web Analyst, E-marketing, web marketing, Online Marketing, Sr. Consultant - Online Marketing/SEM, Search Experience Optimization, Trainer, Google Analytics, Search Engine Marketing, Lead Generation, Landing Page Optimization, Market Research,

Brand Promotions, Market analysis, Monitors market trends and advertising and marketing activities

Experience

Azine Technologies
Digital Marketing Team Lead
May 2018 - Present (3 years 2 months)
Ahmedabad, Gujarat, India

PPC Experts

Analyze client requirement and deliver.

Atlas

Digital Marketing Team Lead June 2017 - May 2018 (1 year)

Ahmedabad Area, India

PPC Experts

Organic Search Strategist Maintain Quality of website

Site Analysis

Social Media Marketing

Analyze client requirement and deliver.

Device developer
Digital Marketing Team Lead
February 2015 - May 2017 (2 years 4 months)
Ahmedabad

Malabar Bay

Lead E-Commerce Operations and Marketing July 2014 - January 2015 (7 months)

Online Marketing, Optimization, Social!Media, Mailers, Paid Promotions
Managing Promotional Banners and Schemes
Managing Products Catalogue
Suggesting and implementing areas of improvements in User Experience

IndiaNIC Infotech Ltd Tech Lead SEO September 2013 - July 2014 (11 months)

Internet marketing, SEM, Web Analyst, Lead Generation, eMarketing Strategist

Verve Systems (Ind) Pvt. Ltd. Sr.SEO, Web Analyst, Internet marketing March 2010 - June 2013 (3 years 4 months)

Brand development, web site traffic growth, Increasing customer loyalty and engagement, web site UI and advertising revenue. Developed brand strategy and statistics systems. Strategic Consulting, including business plan & sales strategy development. Advising new businesses on formation of corporations and business structures, drafting privacy policies and structuring commercial transactions.

DMC Sr.SEO June 2009 - May 2010 (1 year) Sr.SEO

Varologic Technologies Pvt. Ltd. Sr. SEO 2009 - 2009 (less than a year)

Internet marketing & Branding, Social Media Marketing, Web Analyst, E-marketing, web marketing, Online Marketing, Search Marketing, Sr. Consultant - SEO/SEM, SEO Trainer, Google Analytics

IndiaNIC Infotech Ltd SEO Team Leader 2006 - 2009 (3 years)

Internet marketing & Branding, Consultant - SEO/SEM, Web Analyst, SEO Trainer

Sanblue Enterprises Pvt. Ltd Information Resources Executive June 2004 - February 2006 (1 year 9 months)

Worked for Two Year with Sanblue Enterprises Pvt. Ltd as Information Resources Executive.

Education

Gujarat University

B.A, Economics · (2002 - 2005)

P.C. Point

PGDCE · (2000 - 2007)

Jay Somnath Higher Secondary School

10 · (1987 - 2005)

U.C.D. Computer Education

DTP · (1996 - 2002)

Parikh Infosys

DCA · (1985 - 2000)